joeyshaw.com 2010-06-16

# JOEY SHAW - FASHION AND CELEBRITY PHOTOGRAPHER

  | 

Privacy Policy 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers

Here listed JSP will be the Joey Shaw Productions 

**  

  * This policy covers how JSP treats personal information that we collects and receives, including information related to your past use of JSP products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that JSP does not own or control, or to people that JSP does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**  

  * JSP collects personal information when you register with JSP. 
  * JSP collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 
  * JSP automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser. 
  * JSP uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Children**  

  * When a child under age 13 attempts to register with JSP, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian with him/her. 
  * JSP will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 
  * JSP does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * JSP does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with JSP under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help JSP communicate with you about offers from JSP and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing JSP to collect and use their child's information without consenting to JSP sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes; 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of JSP's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if JSP is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, JSP will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * JSP displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * JSP does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * JSP advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 
  * JSP works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

**Confidentiality and Security**  

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * JSP may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your JSP account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, you can contact us at:  
info@joeyshaw.com

JSP is a registered trademark owned by: 

Joey Shaw  
Montecarlo   

|
